right back on the road passing through
Novato Petaluma we're gonna be on 101
for 250 miles so this is this is one of
the best drives I think you could do
with a pilot highway 508 101 highway 80
if you got one Road we're gonna keep you
in the lane
hey what's going on
some people rolling here
and what's up count I just thought it
was so beautiful out that should start
recording again and see if anyone's
woken up Oh what's up Andrew
I'm driving to Arcada today it's amazing
it's 250 miles or so north SF and it's
just highway 101 so open pilot has been
at least 90 percent engaged what's up
man I hope you have initial Sunday
no I'm not I'm not high and I had a cup
of Pete's coffee and that you know
that's pretty strong I guess
after I actually saw Eddie and Eddie in
a Harold like spontaneously in downtown
Berkeley this morning it was kind of
funny
you should you should spend some time
outside today I think it's gonna be
really nice
this whole weekend is like first first
one that starts a feeling summer I mean
I love it up here in Northern California
is a true treasure
man you can see the wine vineyard
starting and everything hey what's going
on
I guess when the camera is facing me
it's like driver monitoring this you
know keeps me in check this is so true
you know I grew up here it's hard to
leave I'm gonna strip myself away a few
years you know I got some gossip got
some things to do in SF before before I
can go for a long time but definitely
want to travel to one of my friends in
Miami right now I don't know if it's to
to stereotypically you know like party
beach town but maybe maybe that's fun
I'm gonna
I'm sure the water is warmer than it is
at Ocean Beach
what's going on
I need more followers than too humid
yeah okay thanks you've been there
sub can drive enough to Arcada
some vineyards asana laughs lightly
I'm not stopping for any wine tours
today this is really good
three more hours to go a couple hundred
miles
but I'll open pilot has been amazing
this whole time
so
I'm sad I can't play music into a
periscope at the same time from my phone
all right I love to play music I met I
met an R&B DJ last night and I'm
listening to his soundcloud it's pretty
pretty good you know I love when people
tell me I have a SoundCloud I never know
how how popular they're gonna be and
this guy's got a following always always
wanted to be me to people you know at
least doing doing mixes and making music
it's too bad as they don't have an
in-n-out burgers on 101 past Santa Rosa
I think it's all their only on five so
you want to get food here you got to
stop at a and I love local diners I love
it I love small-town diners family owned
shops
makes you realize how expensive San
Francisco food is when you go to the
middle of nowhere and you can get a
breakfast plate for like six bucks
I've never been on Bona Arcada I've
never I've never been to Arcada
I'm German past but
I have no idea what to expect in this
town I'm going to I think it's close to
the beach so then I'm going to go to the
beach this afternoon
now what if periscope has six cameras
I don't even want to point this thing at
me because it's honestly it's morbid
hello over Dale
Martita dude
that is I'm gonna if there's not one and
I'm gonna peace out of San Francisco it
started I think I need a little more
cash to bootstrap but I would add I
would absolutely love to like go in an
arcade and like design you know our kids
kind of faded away but I really think
they didn't come back we need a good
amount to show me on yeah this is true I
should get a GoPro like everyone like
everyone uses for their YouTube videos
overtly Chris what's up I'm a pilot up
Northern California right now I'm gonna
keep my phone mounted I'd show you the
EON but you know safety safety is
important but yeah I'm engaged I've been
engaged probably not over 90 95 % of my
highway driving so far this is a 250
mile straight shot up one freeway and
Laurium yeah man I haven't even seen
like what is the latest you can get at
an arcade that's in downtown Emporium
will they have their
put your phone mount on the sunroof and
point it okay baby maybe on the drive
back I'll I'll come up with a better
mount setup because I would I would love
to I would love to have this whole Drive
recorded and as like a time lapse of how
the Aeons doing you know for four hours
maybe I'll buy a groat GoPro up in
Arcata
and like mounted on set up here
oh this is this is one of the nicest
drives I've been on and I've driven I've
driven up 101 many times in my life but
always manually and now they mean the
scenery is so beautiful of just you know
sitting back and enjoying enjoying this
landscape oh it's a nightclub in a stage
Olli should I'm gonna go there for sure
I once at a new parish last night in
Oakland then you on San Pablo it was
pretty good that's where I met I met a
couple people
the crowd wasn't very little the crowd
it was an 18 plus show and I don't know
the 18 to 21 year olds and two stuck in
their heads and so they don't really
dance a lot but there were there were
still some there of you a handful of fun
people there you got a really go into SF
to find the best crowds
are there any PR arcades yet you know is
that a set of thing we can get can I go
like say in a pot and like have all
these like haptic and other like sensory
like elements added on to a VR
experience that's what I really want
timing gauge should be in the UI I agree
that that would be you know I like the
counter up I mean on one hand you know
we don't want to we don't want to
encourage people to like maximize their
engage time in a sense to the point
where it gets unsafe but I think it's
nice to I don't I don't think adding it
to the UI necessarily encourage is that
I think it's actually just a net benefit
for like yeah I want a glance up there
and be like wow you know I've been
engaged for twenty minutes yeah like
it's kind of like having your drive time
back there
virtually Krita so he's still there you
should what do you what do you want on
your Eon UI
maybe not there or if they came deeply
it could be and I think with I mean it
sort of is when we introduce the the
timeline we'll go to it to the secret
stuff but you know it'll be really
visible they're like wow I was engaged
for three hours encourage responsible
engagement yes
yeah I mean we definitely once we have
the driver model ready to ship we should
the driver distraction model of you we
should definitely have that be visible
live of course but also also when you're
driving you know you should know like
boys oh how was the system doing it now
was i doing
you know that you I had yet okay what's
your your head you you you have you have
you know you got here early designer
here so this is this is your chance to
influence
[Music]
pretty clean
yeah I'd agree we're trying to strip
away things and decide what's what do
you really need to you know have visible
because being you know we honestly don't
want you to keep looking at the road we
want to put too much stuff there radar
arrow aligned with the steer angle I see
that would be cool
hold em on that do a prototype current
you guys stay married yeah all I like I
like the plane with rotation so that's a
really good that's a really good idea
we'll see how that looks on the phone
now these are some pretty sharp curves
here so I'm hidden you know staring
temporarily unavailable but I'm just
helping the well a little bit I'm still
engaged
I believe my Civic does have the
displayed additional torque which makes
it you know it feels very safe I've
never had I've never had the car you
know really do anything that I didn't
like and the stereo torque limit is
pretty pretty important to make sure
that they're in space the low floor
remove it eventually you know once we
have a map Plus really just Billy really
just a map we didn't start thinking
about removing Lisa maybe increasing the
torque 100 cars we can safely it's just
it's definitely a big leap from a safety
perspective so we want to be we want to
be very very careful we did take the
Prius up to the racetrack misty of you
if you want to check out the Prius
absolutely : you guys check out our self
racing cars video I Steve the event that
was the fastest Prius that was ever in
that was a very very fun weekend we took
we took the courious it has full
steering torque you know so we're
sending the can message that says I'm in
South Park and then we can we can turn
the whole wheel so we self park the
Prius around the racetrack
I will absolutely I'm just doing it I
want to do more driving periscopes and I
want to get a good mount so you can just
see how the whole the whole system's
behavior
and haven't been to the agent months
this is gonna be fun
I hope there's like cliff views and
stuff take a lot of photos
and I love no one in California
let's you know let's let's make SF like
2 miles tall like Dubai and leave all
this not touched that's what that's
my development plan for for California
right now although hey I should if I
want to play music on periscope what am
I thinking I should just use
I know where we are I love this bridge
you see I used to drive up here with the
family a lot you know go to Sea Ranch
this is this is the path to do so many
beautiful places
[Music]
you